Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize - Series XII: Library
  - Pieter Bruegel. New York: Harry N. Abrams Inc, 1969. [with inserts], cuid28465 (Box XII.41, Folder 573)
  - Pronto: US Retail & Trend Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 5 May 1985., cuid28466 (Box XII.41, Folder 588)
  - Rand McNally Road Atlas. Boston: Rand McNally & Co., 1991., cuid28467 (Box XII.42, Folder 595)
  - Singh, Raghubir. Calcutta. London: Thames and Hudson, 1988., cuid28468 (Box XII.42, Folder 643)
  - Stechow, Wolfgang. Pieter Bruegel the Elder. New York: Harry N. Abrams, [n. d]. [source material see pages 13 and 15. ], undated; cuid28469 (Box XII.42, Folder 657)
  - Steiglitz, Alfred. Georgia O'Keefe. New York: Metropolitan Museum of Modern Art, 1978., cuid28470 (Box XII.42, Folder 658)
  - Ward, Lynd. Storyteller without Words. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1974., cuid28471 (Box XII.43, Folder 715)
  - West Sussex Gazette. 13 May 1993., cuid28472 (Box XII.43, Folder 721)
  - Wingrove, David. The Immortals of Science Fiction. New York: Mayflower Books, 1980., cuid28473 (Box XII.43, Folder 731)
  - Ambrosius, Ernst and Konrad Frenzel. Das Bild der Erde. Bielefeld: Velhagen & Klafing, 1930., cuid28474 (Box XII.44, Folder 29)
  - Arader III, W. Graham. Native Grace. Charlottesville, VI: Thomasson-Grant, 1988., cuid28475 (Box XII.45, Folder 46)
  - Express. [K 2 Aug. 1986, cuid28476 (Box XII.44, Folder 249)
  - ---. [K 2 Sept. 1986, cuid28477 (Box XII.44, Folder 250)
  - The Voice. 26 June 1990., cuid28478 (Box XII.44, Folder 710)
  - National Geographic Atlas of the World. Washington D. C.: National Geographic Society, 1963, cuid28479 (Box XII.45, Folder 498)
  - Standard Atlas of Ford Country. Chicago: Geo. A. Ogle and Co., 1916., cuid28480 (Box XII.45, Folder 653)
  - State Farm Road Atlas. Bloomington, IL: The State Farm Insurance Co., 1939., cuid28481
  - East Village Eye. Vol. V, No. 36, September 1983. /Vol. V, No. 53, May 1984. /Vol. VIII, No. 61, Dec/Jan 1986. /Vol. VIII, No. 63, March 1986., cuid28482 (Box XII.46, Folder 744)
  - Distributed Art Publishers, Catalogs, Spring 1992/Fall 1992., cuid28483 (Box XII.46, Folder 745)
  - Publication: "Your House is Mine, An Act of Resistance 1988-1992." New York: Bullet Space, 1993, 1988-1993; cuid28484 (Box XII.46, Folder 9)
- Mapcase - Series VII: Subjects
  - Subseries C: Announcements
    - Argentina Posters, undated; cuid28485 (Folder 6)
    - "Cop Shoot Cop," Tues Apr 4, Pyramid; "Rock Barricada," Danceteria, April 1, undated; cuid28486 (Folder 8 Left)
    - "Harry Kondoleon / Poet's Corner" Poster, undated; cuid28487 (Folder 9 Right)
    - "Holidays in the Sun" (The Sex Pistols) Poster, undated; cuid28488 (Folder 7)
    - "Larry Clark and Peter Hujar, Frankfurter Kunstverein" Posters, undated; cuid28489 (Folder 10 Right)
    - "Retrospective Posters", undated; cuid28490 (Folder 8)
    - "Silence = Death" / "Positive" Film Screening Poster, undated; cuid28491 (Folder 11 Right)
    - Spanish-language Posters & Rose-Patterned Wrapping Paper, undated; cuid28492 (Folder 9)
    - "Ueber Sofa Auf die Strasse!" Poster, undated; cuid28493 (Folder 12 Right)
    - Various Cultural & Political Posters, undated; cuid28494 (Folder 13 Right)
- Mapcase - Series XI: Art Works
  - Subseries A: Finished/Original
    - "Democracy", undated; cuid28495 (Folder 4 Right)
    - "Hunger", undated; cuid28496 (Folder 7 Left)
    - Offset Plates - "Between C & D", "A Few Months Ago...", undated; cuid28497 (Folder 4)
    - Poster for "Electric Messages Beneath the Sea," Brigitte Engler, The Parallel Window; metal template for "Between C&D" poster, undated; cuid28498 (Folder 5)
    - "Psychiatric Clinic, Court of General Sessions", by David Wojnarowicz and Kiki Smtih, undated; cuid28499 (Flat-file 1.J, Folder 15)
    - "Romulus and Remus Silkscreen Pt. 1", undated; cuid28500 (Folder 6 Left)
    - "Snowflakes - White, Snowman - Dark" Double Lithograph, undated; cuid28501 (Folder 3)
    - Stencil Tool: Skeleton with Pope Hat, undated; cuid28502 (Folder 1 Left, Folder 17 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Bug, undated; cuid28577 (Folder 2 Left)
    - Stencil Tool: Flames with Gorilla, Undated; cuid28590 (Folder 14 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Wolf/Dog Head, undated; cuid28591 (Folder 15 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Abstract Animal Face, undated; cuid28592 (Folder 16 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Pebble Pattern, undated; cuid28593 (Folder 18 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Gorilla Tied to Fence, undated; cuid28594 (Folder 19 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Man's Profile Smoking with Grass, undated; cuid28595 (Folder 20 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Man's Profile, undated; cuid28597 (Folder 20 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Outline of Couple Kissing, undated; cuid28598 (Folder 21 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Couple Kissing, undated; cuid28600 (Folder 22 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Monkey, undated; cuid28601 (Folder 23 Right)
    - Stencil Tool: Couple Kissing - small, undated; cuid28602 (Folder 24 Right)
    - Stencil Image: Falling Man and Map of U.S.A., 1982; cuid28578 (Folder 3 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Skeleton with Pope Hat, undated; cuid28579 (Folder 4 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Barbed Wire, undated; cuid28581 (Folder 6 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Man Fighting Bull, undated; cuid28582 (Folder 7 Left)
    - Stencil Image: "I Wanted One of These Things", undated; cuid28583 (Folder 8 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Soldier Image with Gun, undated; cuid28584 (Folder 9 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Fork, Knife, Plate, undated; cuid28585 (Folder 10 Left)
    - Stencil Image: Fork, Knife, Plate with Figure, undated; cuid28586 (Folder 10 Left)
    - Stencil Tool and Image: Man's Profile Smoking with Grass, undated; cuid28596 (Folder 20 Right)
    - Stencil Tool and Image: Couple Kissing, undated; cuid28599 (Folder 21 Right)
    - Stencil Collage: Folded Arm, undated; cuid28580 (Folder 5 Left)
    - Stencil Collage: "3 Teens Kill 4 - No Motive", undated; cuid28587 (Folder 11 Left)
    - Rough sketches, undated; cuid28588 (Folder 12 Left)
    - Boards with no images, undated; cuid28589 (Folder 13 Left)
    - Various supermarket posters, undated; cuid28503 (Folder 5 Left)
    - Various supermarket posters (some altered), undated; cuid28504 (Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material
    - Source: Bullseye targets; anatomical charts of fish and chicken, undated; cuid28505 (Folder 1 Left, Folder 2 Left, Folder 1)
    - Source: Two Circus posters w/ tigers; poster, "Anatomical Chart of the Acupressure Points" (altered); poster: tribesmen shooting arrows; fragment of evil clowns poster, undated; cuid28506 (Folder 10)
    - Source: Spanish-language posters (3), poster: "The Un-Work Force", undated; cuid28507 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Subseries E: Plans
    - "Vaccinate Your God", undated; cuid28508 (Folder 3 Left)
  - Subseries G: Other People's Art
    - Kiki Smith, "Cause I'm on My Own Time," 4/28/84, 1984; cuid28509 (Folder 11)
- Series XIV: Accretions 2001 - Media
  - VHS: David Wojnarowicz text voice-over, Fear of Disclosure material [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated; cuid28510 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure dancer source material [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated; cuid28511 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - VHS: David Wojnarowicz speech at memorial service for Phil Zwickler 6/1/91 [Estate Project/NYPL], 1991; cuid28512 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure source materials - David Wojnarowicz images 11/1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], cuid28513 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure, David Wojnarowicz and Phil Zwickler 1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], cuid28514 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure, Phil Zwickler and David Wojnarowicz text [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated; cuid28515 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure text - source material 8/1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], cuid28516 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Audiocassette Sony 90: Interview w/ David Wojnarowicz by Adam Kuby 9/14/91 [Gift of Adam Kuby 6/29/01], 1991; cuid28517 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - DAT: JAG #258-Where Evil Dwells., undated; cuid28518 (Box 147, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Accretions 2001 - Biographical
  - Subseries E: Taxes, Receipts, and Legal Documents
    - Correspondence re: Wojnarowicz Published Works and Visual Arts, undated; cuid28519 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 1)
    - Estate Appraisal by P. P. O. W., undated; cuid28520 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 2)
    - Freedman and Fish Correspondence re: Will and Last Testament, undated; cuid28521 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 3)
    - Will and Last Testament, undated; cuid28522 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, undated; cuid28523 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 5)
    - Legal Documents, undated; cuid28524 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, undated; cuid28525 (Box VI.E.2, Folder 7)
    - 16 mm Reel-JAG #240 and #255-Where Evil Dwells., undated; cuid28526 (Box VI.E.3, Folder no number)
- Accretions 2003
  - Notes by David, 1992; cuid28527 (Box 99)
  - Various documents, undated; cuid28528 (Box 99)
  - Plaintiff Exhibit 9: Tongues of Flame, 1990; cuid28529 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Plaintiff's Exhibits: David Wojnarowicz vs. American Family Association and Donald E. Wildmon, 1990; cuid28530 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Posthumous print materials, 2002; cuid28531
  - Personal and Art photographs, ca. 1970 - 1992; cuid28532 (Box 100)
    Inlcudes self portrait photobooth photos, snapshots from France, photos from the Westside piers, polaroids of David in his studio, portraits of David by Peter Hujar, Eric Kroll and others, polaroids of Tom and David, polaroids of stenciled works, etc.
  - Photographs, cuid28533 (Box 101)